wholesalepages.co.uk 2014-02-09

# UK Wholesale - UK Wholesalers Directory: Privacy Policy - Wholesale Pages

Registration | Participation | Cookies | Newsletter | Forum | Security | Termination| Data | Summary

Some basic personal information is required in order to register for membership with Wholesale Pages: 

Name - Your first and last name help us to personalize your online experience. Additionally when we assign you the username and password we need your name to comply with the signing process.   
Email Address - It is required for any correspondence between us and our members.  
Contact Address - This is not essential  
Other Details - No other details are required to become our member 

Participation describes information that is provided "actively" - meaning, you choose to submit this information to us when you join Wholesale Pages, or update your account at any point after having joined. Some other information is provided "passively" \- e.g your I.P address meaning, that we obtain this information when you login to your account and use our services. This is done primarily through the use of "cookies." Cookies are used on to verify your login information, and to optionally store your password in your browser so that you do not need to type it in each time you visit. Any time that you point your browser to a 'members-only' area, Wholesale Pages checks your browser's cookie file to see if you have already logged in, and if you have, you're taken right to the page that you have requested. If not, you'll be directed to the login screen, where you can quickly and easily login to your account, or signup for a new account if you are not yet a member.

Apart from described above (members login) we don't use cookies elsewhere on the site. However we also use Google, as a third-party vendor, which uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html

As a registered user of our newsletter (feature currently not available), your email address is strictly confidential and is not distributed to third parties under any circumstances. Regarding emails from us, you may receive email messages on a regular basis to keep you apprised of your membership status and inform you of new services, updates and offers available to you. Included in each mail will be simple instructions on how to remove yourself from the mailings if you do not wish to receive them in the future. 

Wholesale Pages hosts a message board with an online forum, which is open to general public. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in public forums becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Wholesale Pages site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under its control. Our servers have strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about our users.

You can elect to terminate your membership with us at any time. Simply go to contact us page, and send us a mail with   
your request. Upon termination, your account information will not necessarily be removed entirely from our database and you will be a given a grace period of one week to resume your membership. Furthermore keeping your details helps us to reserve your identity so that no one else can create a new account with your member name or email address, and also allows you the privilege of reactivating your account at a later date if you wish to use our site again.

The Company may hold personal data relating to the transactions you enter with us. We will disclose the data to a party only to assist your transactions. The Company may use your personal data to let you know about the product and price changes. At all times we will observe the requirements imposed by the Data Protection Act 1998 and we will provide the appropriate security to maintain the confidentiality of your personal data. Although strict measures have been put in place to keep your information confidential, however due to unforeseen circumstances or web related attack on our site we do not guarantee complete security of your information and we will not be held responsible if such a situation may arise.

In this electronic era, when personal information can easily be obtained through various sources, Wholesale Pages appreciates the sensitivity of any private information that you disclose to us. It is our intention to treat your account information with the highest level of care.
